

CONTACT

AdilKhanEngineer72@gmail.com

0344-344-4141

Commercial Market Room 311 Mukhtar Plaza Satellite Town Rawalpindi

SKILLS

Hml/Hml5 Graphic design Ui / UX design CSS 3 **JavaScript** WordPress (CMS) Magento (CMS) Php Scripting My SQL OOP Php Ajax/Xml/Json Adobe illustrator Adobe PhotoShop **Hybrid Apps Db Structure Design** Ajax/Xml/Json Codeigniter **REQ** Implementation

WP Theme Dvp

HOBBIES

Photography | Reading | Writing Stories Video Games | Cooking | Chess Traveling Music | Internet Surfing Sports : Badminton, Table Tennis, FootballVolunteering to the "red cross" Birdwatching

INTERESTED IN

Server-Side Backend Programming Front-End UI / UX Designing Logo Designing / Making GIF Artificial Inteligence

PASSIONATE USE OF

Hp Netbook | Windows(10) | Keypad Google Chrome | Microsoft Office

SPECIALITIES

Software Development | Database Connectivity | Project Management DataBase Designing

SOFTWARE ENGINEER | WEB DEVELOPER

ADIL KHAN

Father Name Rehmat Ali
Date of Birth 02 January,1994
CNIC # 15604-0347147-3

Gender Male

Language Urdu, English, Punjabi

Nationality Pakistani Religion Islam

CAREER SUMMERY

BS.SE(Software Engineering) with 1 (One) YearDiploma in IT. More Than 2 (Two) Year of Working experience as Backend Developer And 1 (One) year working experience as Web Designer. Total 3 Three Years of Experience.

Besides Syntax knowledge like PHP, JAVASCRIPT, I also have good logic of the Programming Language and making Architecture on back-end as well as in Designing a Database in efficient way for Data. Ability to develop and design webpages and websites to make them functional.

Knowledge of the international web standards and protocols and experience to work within the compliance.

Experience of drafting end-user and technical manuals.

Multi-tasking ability with the experience of handling multiple projects at a time. Experience integrating websites with social networking sites like Facebook etc.

Team player with experience of training the new joiners.

Excellent communication and inter-personal skills with experience of interacting with the end-users and resolving their queries to their satisfaction. Ability to grasp the ideas of the clients and implement in the same direction.

EDUCATION

2013 - 2017 Bsc (Hons) - Software Engineering

University of Swat

3.1 (GPA)

1998 - 2012 High School

Al-Razi School And College

78 (Percentage)

 AJK

WORK EXPERIENCE

Feb 2018- Present Back-End Web Developer

AZAM Systems

Web Development, PMS (ERP) Making in Codeigniter, Server Administration and

Management, On-Page SEO.

Oct 2016 - Jan 2018 Web Developer And Designer

MAF Software And Technologies

Web Development, Programming Teaching, Websites Management, Basic IT Teaching.

Dec 2015 - Jan 2017 Independent Software Developer

Self Employee

Freelancing at Fiverr

Feb 2015 - Dec 2015 Learner Internee Developer

Maxtech

Started as Internee As a Web Developer

OverAll Information (Portfolio, Projects, Exp. Certifiactes) Link > > www.adil.stackwiser.net/